<resources>
    <string name="sample">Please select a Band and click for more details of the band..!!!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Rock On!</string>
    <string name="ledZeppelinString">Led Zeppelin</string>
    <string name="beatlesString">The Beatles</string>
    <string name="pinkFloydString">Pink Floyd</string>
    <string name="queenString">Queen</string>
    <string name="metallicaString">Metallica</string>

    <string name="lzDesc"><b>Led Zeppelin</b> were an English rock band formed in London in 1968. The group consisted of guitarist
        Jimmy Page, singer Robert Plant, bassist and keyboardist John Paul Jones, and drummer John Bonham. The band\'s heavy,
        guitar-driven sound, rooted in blues and psychedelia on their early albums, has earned them recognition as one of the
        progenitors of heavy metal, though their unique style drew from a wide variety of influences, including folk music.
        After changing their name from the New Yardbirds, Led Zeppelin signed a deal with Atlantic Records that afforded them
        considerable artistic freedom. Although the group was initially unpopular with critics, they achieved significant commercial
        success with albums such as Led Zeppelin (1969), Led Zeppelin II (1969), Led Zeppelin III (1970), Led Zeppelin IV (1971),
        Houses of the Holy (1973), and Physical Graffiti (1975). Their fourth album, which features the track "Stairway to Heaven",
        is among the most popular and influential works in rock music, and it helped to secure the group\'s popularity.
        Page wrote most of Led Zeppelin\'s music, particularly early in their career, while Plant generally supplied the lyrics. Jones\'
        keyboard-based compositions later became central to the group\'s catalogue, which featured increasing experimentation. The
        latter half of their career saw a series of record-breaking tours that earned the group a reputation for excess and debauchery.
        Although they remained commercially and critically successful, their output and touring schedule were limited during the
        late 1970s, and the group disbanded following Bonham\'s death from alcohol-related asphyxia in 1980.\n\nLed Zeppelin are widely considered one of the most successful, innovative, and influential rock groups in history.
        They are one of the best-selling music artists in the history of audio recording; various sources estimate the group\'s
        record sales at 200 to 300 million units worldwide. Rolling Stone magazine described them as "the heaviest band of all time",
        "the biggest band of the Seventies", and "unquestionably one of the most enduring bands in rock history". They were
        inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1995; the museum\'s biography of the band states that they were "as influential"
        during the 1970s as the Beatles were during the 1960s.</string>
    <string name="tbDesc"><b>The Beatles</b> were an English rock band, formed in Liverpool in 1960. With members John Lennon,
        Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr, they became widely regarded as the foremost and most influential act of the
        rock era. Rooted in skiffle, beat, and 1950s rock and roll, the Beatles later experimented with several genres, ranging
        from pop ballads and Indian music to psychedelia and hard rock, often incorporating classical elements in innovative ways.
        In the early 1960s, their enormous popularity first emerged as "Beatlemania", but as the group\'s music grew in sophistication,
        led by primary songwriters Lennon and McCartney, they came to be perceived as an embodiment of the ideals shared by the
        counterculture of the 1960s.\n\nThe Beatles built their reputation playing clubs in Liverpool and Hamburg over a three-year period from 1960, with
        Stuart Sutcliffe initially serving as bass player. The core of Lennon, McCartney and Harrison went through a succession
        of drummers, most notably Pete Best, before asking Starr to join them. Manager Brian Epstein moulded them into a professional
        act and producer George Martin enhanced their musical potential. They gained popularity in the United Kingdom after their
        first hit, "Love Me Do", in late 1962. They acquired the nickname "the Fab Four" as Beatlemania grew in Britain over the
        following year, and by early 1964 they had become international stars, leading the "British Invasion" of the United States
        pop market. From 1965 onwards, the Beatles produced what many consider their finest material, including the innovative and
        widely influential albums Rubber Soul (1965), Revolver (1966), Sgt. Pepper\'s Lonely Hearts Club Band (1967), The Beatles
        (commonly known as the White Album, 1968) and Abbey Road (1969).</string>
    <string name="pfDesc"><b>Pink Floyd</b> were an English rock band formed in London. They achieved international acclaim with their
        progressive and psychedelic music. Distinguished by their use of philosophical lyrics, sonic experimentation, extended
        compositions and elaborate live shows, they are one of the most commercially successful and musically influential groups
        in the history of popular music.\n\nPink Floyd were founded in 1965 by students Syd Barrett, Nick Mason, Roger Waters, and Richard Wright. They gained popularity
        performing in London\'s underground music scene during the late 1960s, and under Barrett\'s leadership released two charting
        singles and a successful debut album, The Piper at the Gates of Dawn (1967). David Gilmour joined as a fifth member in
        December 1967; Barrett left the band in April 1968 due to deteriorating mental health. Waters became the band\'s primary
        lyricist and, by the mid-1970s, their dominant songwriter, devising the concepts behind their critically and commercially
        successful albums The Dark Side of the Moon (1973), Wish You Were Here (1975), Animals (1977), The Wall (1979) and The Final
        Cut (1983). The Dark Side of the Moon and The Wall became two of the best-selling albums of all time.</string>
    <string name="queenDesc"><b>Queen</b> are a British rock band that formed in London in 1970. The classic line-up was Freddie Mercury
        (lead vocals, piano), Brian May (guitar, vocals), Roger Taylor (drums, vocals), and John Deacon (bass guitar). Queen\'s
        earliest works were influenced by progressive rock, hard rock and heavy metal, but the band gradually ventured into more
        conventional and radio-friendly works by incorporating further styles, such as arena rock and pop rock, into their music.
        Before forming Queen, Brian May and Roger Taylor had played together in a band named Smile. Freddie Mercury (then known by
        his birth name of Farrokh "Freddie" Bulsara) was a fan of Smile and encouraged them to experiment with more elaborate stage
        and recording techniques. Mercury joined the band in 1970, suggested "Queen" as a new band name, and adopted his familiar
        stage name. John Deacon was recruited prior to recording their eponymous debut album in 1973. Queen first charted in the UK
        with their second album, Queen II, in 1974, but it was the release of Sheer Heart Attack later that year and A Night at the
        Opera in 1975 which brought them international success. The latter featured "Bohemian Rhapsody", which stayed at number one
        in the UK for nine weeks and popularised the music video. Their 1977 album, News of the World, contained "We Will Rock You"
        and "We Are the Champions", which have become anthems at sporting events. By the early 1980s, Queen were one of the biggest
        stadium rock bands in the world.</string>
    <string name="metDesc"><b>Metallica</b> is an American heavy metal band formed in Los Angeles, California. Metallica was formed in 1981
        when vocalist/guitarist James Hetfield responded to an advertisement posted by drummer Lars Ulrich in a local newspaper. The
        band\'s current line-up comprises founding members Hetfield and Ulrich, longtime lead guitarist Kirk Hammett and bassist Robert
        Trujillo. Lead guitarist Dave Mustaine and bassists Ron McGovney, Cliff Burton and Jason Newsted are former members of the band.
        Metallica collaborated over a long period with producer Bob Rock, who produced all of the band\'s albums from 1990 to 2003 and
        served as a temporary bassist between the departure of Newsted and the hiring of Trujillo.\n\nThe band\'s fast tempos, instrumentals, and aggressive musicianship placed them as one of the founding "big four" bands of
        thrash metal, alongside Anthrax, Megadeth, and Slayer. The band earned a growing fan base in the underground music community
        and won critical acclaim with its first four albums; their third album Master of Puppets (1986) was described as one of the
        most influential and heaviest of thrash metal albums. Metallica achieved substantial commercial success with its eponymous
        fifth album Metallica (1991), which debuted at number one on the Billboard 200. With this release the band expanded its musical
        direction, resulting in an album that appealed to a more mainstream audience. In 2000, Metallica was among a number of artists
        who filed a lawsuit against Napster for sharing the band\'s copyright-protected material for free without consent from any
        band member. A settlement was reached and Napster became a pay-to-use service. Despite reaching number one on the Billboard 200,
        the release of St. Anger (2003) alienated many fans with the exclusion of guitar solos and the "steel-sounding" snare drum.
        A film titled Some Kind of Monster documented the recording of St. Anger and the tensions within the band during that time.
        In 2009,Metallica was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</string>
</resources>
